<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on From Now On</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on From Now On</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 18:46:17 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Literate Review of Related Works on NAI (Network-Application Integration)</title>
      <link>/post/nai-related-work-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 18:46:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/nai-related-work-summary/</guid>
      <description>Recently, my research interest moves to NAI (Network-Application Integration), which we think will become a hot direction of networking systems in the next few years. While it is not a totally new topic, because of emerging application service architectures (e.g., CDN, MEC, Live Video Streaming, Cloud Gaming) and networking architectures (e.g., Programmable Dataplane, SD-WAN, Segment Routing, New IP), previous works may not work very well.
To better understand new challenges on this direction, we make this literate review.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Present My SIGCOMM Poster in a Hubs VR Room</title>
      <link>/post/sigcomm2020-poster-present/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 18:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/sigcomm2020-poster-present/</guid>
      <description>2020 is an amazing year when we experienced many many &amp;ldquo;first times&amp;rdquo;. Good news and bad news.
First time, my first-author poster COC: Hierarchical Coflow Ordering for WAN Bandwidth Optimization in Inter-Data Center was accepted by SIGCOMM. First time, I participated SRC (Student Research Competition) in SIGCOMM. First time, I presented a poster in a Hubs VR room.
Yes, SIGCOMM poster/demo committee decided to use Mozilla Hubs to present each poster/demo online this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Reading List Resuming Plan</title>
      <link>/post/resume-research-reading-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 11:41:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/resume-research-reading-list/</guid>
      <description>I have read a bunch of research papers in the past few years. But I fail to remember most of them because of the lack of summary and better organization. It is time to resume the research reading list for myself.
Although there are already several very good public reading lists about computer networking, e.g., Cristian Lumezanu&amp;rsquo;s SDN Reading List and Richard Yang&amp;rsquo;s Lecture, they are so general that they do not match my research interests very well.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>