<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts | From Now On</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
      <atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Posts</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 18:46:17 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/logo_hu3e34e5a2bb4f4cfff97a5b00f921c36c_36701_300x300_fit_lanczos_2.png</url>
      <title>Posts</title>
      <link>/post/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Literate Review of Related Works on NAI (Network-Application Integration)</title>
      <link>/post/nai-related-work-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 18:46:17 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/nai-related-work-summary/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Recently, my research interest moves to NAI (Network-Application
Integration), which we think will become a hot direction of networking
systems in the next few years. While it is not a totally new topic, because
of emerging application service architectures (&lt;em&gt;e.g.&lt;/em&gt;, CDN, MEC, Live Video
Streaming, Cloud Gaming) and networking architectures (&lt;em&gt;e.g.&lt;/em&gt;, Programmable
Dataplane, SD-WAN, Segment Routing, New IP), previous works may not work very
well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To better understand new challenges on this direction, we make this literate
review. For each particular existing work, we try to figure out the following
questions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What is its design space?
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In its design, which information is required to be fed by applications?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In its design, which information is required to be exposed by the network?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What is its potential issues?
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If possible, how easily can it be extended to other use cases?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Why it cannot work well in some cases?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;related-works&#34;&gt;Related Works&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a starting point, we collect related works published on CoNEXT, SOSP,
NSDI, and SIGCOMM from 2007 to 2019.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The current literate review covers papers in the following list. And the list
may grow in the future, if we find more highly related works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;bibtex_display&#34; bibtexkeys=&#34;Wiser|PVM|CIPT|Timecard|Footprint|VDX|Akamai2018|Taiji|E2E&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;review-cards&#34;&gt;Review Cards&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;wiser&#34;&gt;Wiser&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;High-level Goal&lt;/strong&gt;: design a practical interdomain routing protocol that
enables ISPs to jointly control routing and compute good end-to-end paths
while acting in their own interest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$\text{cost}_I = \min_{paths} (\sum_{p \in paths} \text{traffic}_I(p) \times \text{intcost}_I(p))$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Symbol&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Description&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$I$&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;An ISP&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$paths$&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;All possible end-to-end paths&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$\text{cost}_I$&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Expected external cost for ISP $I$&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$\text{traffic}_I(p)$&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;The rate of traffic carried along path $p$ over some period&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$\text{intcost}_I(p)$&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;The internal cost of path $p$ in ISP $I$&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Basic Idea&lt;/strong&gt;: Each ISP estimate its own external cost and advertise to its
neighbors the total cost to reach the destination. And each router selects
the lowest cost path.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Potential Extension to NAI&lt;/strong&gt;: For ISPs serving their own CDN, those ISPs can
compute their own internal cost based on their CDN loads.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Limitation&lt;/strong&gt;: Lowest-cost routing per destination may lead to congestion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;path-verification-mechanism-pvm&#34;&gt;Path Verification Mechanism (PVM)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;cooperative-ip-transit-cipt&#34;&gt;Cooperative IP Transit (CIPT)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;timecard&#34;&gt;Timecard&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;timecard-fig1.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;e2e&#34;&gt;E2E&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;e2e-fig2.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;e2e-fig11.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Present My SIGCOMM Poster in a Hubs VR Room</title>
      <link>/post/sigcomm2020-poster-present/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 18:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/sigcomm2020-poster-present/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;2020 is an amazing year when we experienced many many &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;first times&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;. Good
news and bad news.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First time, my first-author poster &lt;em&gt;COC: Hierarchical Coflow Ordering for WAN
Bandwidth Optimization in Inter-Data Center&lt;/em&gt; was accepted by SIGCOMM. First
time, I participated SRC (Student Research Competition) in SIGCOMM. First
time, I presented a poster in a 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://hubs.mozilla.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Hubs&lt;/a&gt; VR room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, SIGCOMM poster/demo committee decided to use 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://hubs.mozilla.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Mozilla
Hubs&lt;/a&gt; to present each poster/demo online this
year. Each author was required to host a Hubs VR room and present his/her
work in his/her own VR room online. What does it mean? It means more
workload! You have to set up a VR room besides your pre-print A0 poster.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The SIGCOMM poster/demo session took place over August 11-12 from
4:30pm-5:30pm ET. The time slots were friendly to me, as I was still stuck in
US. But I believe they were not to many people in Asia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, such a experiencement is interesting enough, although some of my
audiences failed to join the VR room. I guess they were using some lower
performance cellphones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The SRC is also interesting enough. I met 3 or 4 jurors. Some of them did not
just ask questions, but also gave some helpful comments. I really appreciate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I believe a major benefit of using the online room is that there is no limit
about the place. It does not mean the room can hold unlimited number of
audiences. It means the time slot is unlimited. This online room is fully
occupied by yourself. Nobody can take it. Whenever you want to show
something, the room is just there. So if you are interested in what I am
working on, although the SIGCOMM conference has ended, you can still feel
free to stop by my VR room and take a look at my work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the link to my poster VR room: &lt;a href=&#34;https://hub.link/wjYrtZ3&#34;&gt;https://hub.link/wjYrtZ3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I put the original PDF files of the 2-page abstract and the A0 poster in this
room. You can feel free to download them without my approval. If you have any
questions, just drop me an email to &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:jensen@jensen-zhang.site&#34;&gt;jensen@jensen-zhang.site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can also send me an email to request a slot if you want a VR chat. I can
meet you in the VR room and talk to you about my work online. Don&amp;rsquo;t be shy.
Maybe we can be very good friends.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Reading List Resuming Plan</title>
      <link>/post/resume-research-reading-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 11:41:17 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/resume-research-reading-list/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have read a bunch of research papers in the past few years. But I fail to
remember most of them because of the lack of summary and better organization. It
is time to resume the research reading list for myself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although there are already several very good public reading lists about computer
networking, e.g., 
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.nec-labs.com/~lume&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Cristian Lumezanu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rsquo;s 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://sites.google.com/site/sdnreadinglist/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;SDN Reading List&lt;/a&gt;
and 
&lt;a href=&#34;http://cs.yale.edu/homes/yry&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Richard Yang&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rsquo;s 
&lt;a href=&#34;http://zoo.cs.yale.edu/classes/cs434/cs434-2019-spring/schedule.shtml&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Lecture&lt;/a&gt;, they are so
general that they do not match my research interests very well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, it is hard to summarize a very comprehensive reading list
immediately. But by following my recent research topics, I will complete the
reading list little by little. And I will begin from the following topic: the
interdomain network optimization for large-scale data analytics systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;reading-list&#34;&gt;Reading List&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;bibtex_display&#34; bibtexkeys=&#34;chowdhury2014efficient|chowdhury2015efficient|zhang2016coda|agarwal2018sincronia|chowdhury2016|pu2015|sambasivan2017&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;quick-highlights-of-key-techniques&#34;&gt;Quick Highlights of Key Techniques&lt;/h2&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
