<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>poster | From Now On</title>
    <link>/tags/poster/</link>
      <atom:link href="/tags/poster/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>poster</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 18:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/logo_hu3e34e5a2bb4f4cfff97a5b00f921c36c_36701_300x300_fit_lanczos_2.png</url>
      <title>poster</title>
      <link>/tags/poster/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Present My SIGCOMM Poster in a Hubs VR Room</title>
      <link>/post/sigcomm2020-poster-present/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 18:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/sigcomm2020-poster-present/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;2020 is an amazing year when we experienced many many &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;first times&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;. Good
news and bad news.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First time, my first-author poster &lt;em&gt;COC: Hierarchical Coflow Ordering for WAN
Bandwidth Optimization in Inter-Data Center&lt;/em&gt; was accepted by SIGCOMM. First
time, I participated SRC (Student Research Competition) in SIGCOMM. First
time, I presented a poster in a 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://hubs.mozilla.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Hubs&lt;/a&gt; VR room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, SIGCOMM poster/demo committee decided to use 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://hubs.mozilla.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Mozilla
Hubs&lt;/a&gt; to present each poster/demo online this
year. Each author was required to host a Hubs VR room and present his/her
work in his/her own VR room online. What does it mean? It means more
workload! You have to set up a VR room besides your pre-print A0 poster.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The SIGCOMM poster/demo session took place over August 11-12 from
4:30pm-5:30pm ET. The time slots were friendly to me, as I was still stuck in
US. But I believe they were not to many people in Asia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, such a experiencement is interesting enough, although some of my
audiences failed to join the VR room. I guess they were using some lower
performance cellphones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The SRC is also interesting enough. I met 3 or 4 jurors. Some of them did not
just ask questions, but also gave some helpful comments. I really appreciate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I believe a major benefit of using the online room is that there is no limit
about the place. It does not mean the room can hold unlimited number of
audiences. It means the time slot is unlimited. This online room is fully
occupied by yourself. Nobody can take it. Whenever you want to show
something, the room is just there. So if you are interested in what I am
working on, although the SIGCOMM conference has ended, you can still feel
free to stop by my VR room and take a look at my work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the link to my poster VR room: &lt;a href=&#34;https://hub.link/wjYrtZ3&#34;&gt;https://hub.link/wjYrtZ3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I put the original PDF files of the 2-page abstract and the A0 poster in this
room. You can feel free to download them without my approval. If you have any
questions, just drop me an email to &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:jensen@jensen-zhang.site&#34;&gt;jensen@jensen-zhang.site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can also send me an email to request a slot if you want a VR chat. I can
meet you in the VR room and talk to you about my work online. Don&amp;rsquo;t be shy.
Maybe we can be very good friends.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
